첫 경험을...
여자랑 했다구요?
So your first sexual experience
was with a woman?
15살 때 친구 루스하고요
독한 사이다 먹고 취했거든요
I was 15.
It was my best friend, Ruth.
And we got drunk on that hard cider.
어쩌다 보니까...
그렇게 돼버렸어요
And then suddenly,
we were making out.
다시 말해봐요
Tell it again.
Seriously.
정말루요
저 여자는 섹스 얘기 말고는
할 얘기가 없나봐
Can that woman talk
about anything else but sex?
아냐, 아까는 지리 얘기도
했었어
Yeah, sure. Earlier she was
talking about geography.
'그거' 했던 나라 이름
늘어놓은 거잖아
She was listing the countries
she's done it in.
I think we all
learned something.
어쨌든 공부가 됐잖아
얘들아, 이것 봐라
Hey, you guys! Look what I found!
엄마가 쓴 거야
That's my mom's writing. Look.
"Me and Frank and Phoebe,
graduation, 1965."
'프랭크, 피비와 함께
1965년 졸업식'
무슨 뜻인지 알겠어?
-Do you know what that means?
-That you're actually 50?
너 50살이라고?
이 피비는 내가 아냐
엄마 친구지
That's not "me" Phoebe.
That's her pal, Phoebe.
According to her yearbook,
they were BFF.
학교 연감 보니까
두 분이 '영짝'이었더라구
Best Friends Forever.
'영원한 짝궁'
That's great!
잘됐다
이 아줌마 만나면 부모님
얘길 들을 수 있을 거야
I know! She probably has all kinds
of stories about my parents.
아빠가 어디 계신지
알지도 모르지
She might know where my dad is.
알아봤더니 해변 근처에
사신대, 우리 주말에 가자
I looked her up.
She lives by the beach.
Maybe this weekend we can
go there.
- 그래
- 그러자
-Shoot, I can't go. I have to work.
-That's too bad.
- 난 일 있어서 못 가
- 이런...
쌤통이다
Big fat bummer.
좋아, 그럼 내일 몬택으로
가는 거다
So tomorrow we'll drive out
to Montauk.
보니 거기서 섹스했대
Hey, Bonnie had sex there!
The One At the Beach
Would you look at them?
저 사람들 봐
난 남자친구 못 사귈 거야
I'm never gonna find
a boyfriend again.
I'm gonna die an old maid.
노처녀로 죽을 거야
그냥 노처녀로 죽진 않아
You're not gonna die an old maid.
노처녀 요리사라면 몰라도
Maybe an old spinster cook.
고맙다
-Thanks.
-Besides, worse comes to worse...
최악의 경우엔 내가
네 남자친구가 될 수도 있어
... I'll be your boyfriend.
그래
Yeah, right.
뭐가 그렇게 웃겨?
Why is that so funny?
농담한 거잖아
그래서 웃는 거야
You made a joke, right?
So I laughed.
너무 웃는다
A little too hard.
왜, 난 남자친구 감이 못돼?
Am I not boyfriend material?
아니, 넌 챈들러잖아
You're Chandler.
넌 챈들러라구!
You know. Chandler!
좋아, 내 이름을 부르면서
때렸다 이거지
Okay, so we've established
my name, and hit me.
우리가 소개팅을 한다고 쳐
내가 문을 두드리면서
But say we weren't friends.
Say it's a blind date.
I show up at your door and I'm,
like, "Hey, nice to meet you."
이러는 거야
안녕, 반가워요, 헤이
이상한 목소리 내는 사람은
무서워서 싫어
I'd probably be scared of a guy
using a fake voice.
- 얘들아
- 먹을 거 샀구나
Oh, good. You bought food.
아니, 내 짐이야
No, just my luggage.
- 얘들아
- 안녕
좋아, 야호!
이번 주엔 좋은 일이
많이 생기네
I am having the best karma this week.
부모님 친구 소식 알게 된 것도
고마운데 고객이 집을 빌려준대
I find this woman
who knew my parents...
...and then my client
gives me his beach house.
차로 들이받은
오토바이 퀵서비스는?
What about that bike
messenger you hit?
Oh, I wasn't talking about his karma.
그 얘길 하는 게 아니잖아
- 안녕
모자 좀 봐
Hey, check out the hat!
잠깐, 나 이 모자 알아
Wait a minute, I know that hat.
전에 이 모자에 탄 적 있어
I was taken aboard that hat.
나한테 실험을 했어
They did experiments on me.
난 아이를 못 낳아
I can't have children!
농담 말고,
모자는 어디서 났어?
Seriously, where did you get the hat?
Ross gave it to me.
로스가 줬어
잘 어울리잖아
I think she looks good.
고마워
산 거야, 아님 게임에서
따준 거야?
Did he buy it for you...
...or win it for you?
내 패션이 맘에 안 드는
모양인데
Excuse me,
my fashion-impaired friends...
모자 심기를 건드리지
말아 줘
... I'm here to tell you
hats are back.
모자들이 모여서 대빵 큰
거인 모자를 만들었거든
And this time, they've ganged up
and formed one giant super-hat.
Go, go, go!
빨리 들어가
다들 모자 밑으로 들어와!
Now everybody wants to be
under the hat!
웬 모래가 이렇게 많아?
What's with all this sand?
홍수 여파가 있을지
모른댔어
Bob said there might be flood damage.
아님 엄청 큰
고양이가 있던가
Either that or he has
a really big cat.
좀 별나긴 하죠
It's kind of an unusual house.
침실 세 개에 욕실은 하나도
없으니까요
It has three beautiful bedrooms
and no baths.
하지만 바로 앞이 바다예요
But, you know, the ocean
is right there.
- 그러니까...
- 똑똑
IKnock, knock, knock.
잠깐만요, 들어와요
Hang on.
Come in, come in.
생각해보고 전화해줘요
Think about it and call me back.
- 아줌마가 피비 애보트예요?
- 그런데요
Are you Phoebe Abbott?
Surprise, Phoebe Abbott!
I'm your best friend's daughter!
피비 애보트 아줌마
전 아줌마 친구 딸이에요
어윈의 딸이야?
You're lrwin's daughter?
아뇨, 아줌마 옛날 친구요
I mean your old best friend.
Here.
릴리라고 고등학교 친구
아시죠?
-Lily? From high school? Remember?
-Oh, God, Lily. Yes.
맙소사, 릴리
그럼 당연히 알지
Of course I remember Lily.
그러면 아가씨는...
Then you must be
피비예요, 피비
Phoebe, Phoebe.
아줌마 이름을 땄나봐요
She named me after you, I guess.
프랭크도 있네
Wow. Well.
Look, there's Frank!
그래요, 그 분이 우리 아빠
프랭크예요
Yeah! Yes! Yes, yes!
That's my dad. That's Frank!
죄송해요
너무 흥분해서...
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy.
진정하고 카운터에 쿠키
있으니까 먹어
Take it easy.
If you want, there's cookies.
Or sangria! I could make sangria!
레모네이트 만들어줘?
- 아니에요
- 난...
Sorry. Cookies are good, thanks.
쿠키면 돼요
어쨌든...
Anyway, I've been
looking for my father.
지금 아빠를 찾고 있는데
소식 들었거나
만난 적 있어요?
-Have you heard from him or seen him?
-Oh, no, I'm sorry.
아니, 미안해
학교 졸업하고
연락이 다 끊겼어
I lost track of everybody
after high school.
그래요?
저희 부모님 얘기 좀 해주세요
전부 다요
Well, so tell me everything
about my parents. Everything.
우린 항상 붙어 다녔어
애들이 별명을 붙여줄 정도였지
Oh, well, you know,
we were always together.
-The other kids had a nickname for us.
-What was it?
뭐라고 불렀는데요?
The Three Losers.
못난이 삼총사
가엾은 릴리
Oh, poor Lily.
얘기 다 들었어
아가씨도 힘들었을 거야
I heard what happened. That must
have been just terrible for you...
엄마를 그렇게 잃어서...
...Iosing your mother that way.
네, 아뇨
대단치도 않죠
Yeah, no, it was great.
비오는 날 무슨 게임이
좋은 줄 알아?
You know what a really good
rainy-day game is?
뭔데?
옷 벗기기 게임
I mean, naked game.
우리 옷 벗기기 포커 하자
We should play strip poker.
- 미쳤니?
- 싫어
Are you crazy?
하자, 놀러 왔으면 놀아야지
그게 법이야
Come on. When you go away,
you have to play. It's, like, a law.
- 다 됐다
- 고마워
-All done.
-Thank you.
다음 선수
Okay. Who's next?
싫어
안 해
No way!
나 심심해 죽겠어
저번엔 바르라고 했잖아
Come on, please. I'm bored.
You let me do it once before.
그게 이번 주말의 법이라도
되는 거야?
Well, if that's the rule
this weekend....
싫어
-Get away.
-Take it like a man. Come on!
- 제발 한번만
- 저리 가
- 안돼
- 이리 와
맞을래?
Big bullies!
싫어, 싫어, 싫어...
- 얘들아
- 안녕
- 재미 좋니?
- 재미없어 죽겠어
How are we doing?
Bored and bored.
You know what naked card game's
never boring?
옷 벗기기 포커하면 재밌어
싫어!
So what's Phoebe like?
피비는 어때?
친절하고 다정하지
모니카는 어떠니?
I'm kind, caring and sweet.
What's Monica like?
No, the other Phoebe.
The one you went to see?
아니, 다른 피비 말야
만나러 갔던 사람
아빠가 어디 계신지
아시는 것 같아
I think she knows where my dad is!
- 잘됐다
- 진짜?
Cool!
어디 계시는데?
Where is he?
몇 년째 소식 못 들었다고
거짓말하는데
She was pretending she hasn't
heard from him...
냉장고에서 이 사진을
찾았어
...but I found this picture.
봐, 이 사진 보니까 어때?
Isn't this what he would
look like now?
- 낯이 익어
- 그렇지?
Totally familiar.
- 그러게
- 와우!
왜 거짓말을 하는데?
Why would she lie to you?
몰라, 내일 저녁 먹기로
했으니까 그때 말하겠지
We're having dinner tomorrow.
Maybe she'll tell me then.
아빠한테 시간을 주고
싶어서 그런지도 몰라
Maybe she just wanted
to give him time...
나한테 선물이라도 사주라고
...to buy me presents.
I don't know.
So you're all bored?
- 심심해 죽겠다고?
- 그래
눈감고 한 사람 지목하면,
재미있는 게임 생각해내기
I'll close my eyes and point
to someone. Whoever it is...
... has to think of something
fun to do. And we have to do it.
꼭 해야 돼
그래, 빨리 흩어져
Okay! Fan out! Fan out!
좋아
이것도 재밌다
You know, we could just do this!
좋아...
옷 벗기기 포커
We all have to play strip poker?
야호!
Strip Happy Days Game?
'행복한 날' 게임?
카드를 찾을 수가 있어야지
아님 '뜨개질' 카드 밖에 없어
I couldn't find cards, so it was this
or Strip Bag-Of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
좋아
Done.
엄지 두 개를 들어올린다
2점이야, 좋아
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up.
Collect two cool points."
5점이 되면 한 사람을
지목해서 옷을 벗길 수 있어
Get five points, you get to make
someone take off one item of clothing.
아직 하나도 못 벗겼지?
너무 기대된다
It hasn't happened yet,
but we're very excited.
좋았어
Okay, come on.
선사시대 법정에서 쓰던
전자석 두 개 나와라
Daddy needs a new electromagnetic
microscope for Prehistoric Forensics.
좋아
"Take Pinky Tuscadero up
to lnspiration Point.
분홍색 터스커니 점수 추가
3점이다, 예!
Collect three cool points." Yeah!
그럼 5점이네
Which gives me five.
어디... 누구 옷을 벗길까
And let's see, who is gonna lose
their clothes?
옷 벗기기 포커의 호프,
조이 트리비아니!
I think I pick our strip poker
sponsor, Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
좋아하지 마
신발만 벗을 거야
All right, relax. It's just a shoe.
"아놀드 바에서 밴드가
연주한다" 3점이야
"Your band is playing at Arnold's.
Collect three cool points."
그럼 나 5점 됐으니까
조이, 너 팬티 벗어
Which means I have five and
that means I get Joey's boxers.
나만 집중공격하려고?
잘 생각하는 게 좋을걸
Fine. Gang up on me.
I got you all,
right where I want you.
빨리 벗어
Come on! Take them off!
좀 추워서 그러는데
Actually, it's kind of cold.
팬티는 그냥 입고 있을 테니까
그것만 살짝 보면 안돼?
What if I keep them on and
give you a peek at the good stuff?
좋아
난 마가리타 만들어야지
I'm gonna make more margaritas.
뭐하는 거야?
나 취하게 하려고?
What are you doing?
Trying to get me drunk?
마가리타 만드는 거야
I'm just making margaritas.
나도 도와줘야지
Think I'll help her out.
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 뭐가?
What is going on here?
What?
- 발톱을 칠하고...
- 아냐
You're painting his toenails.
Chasing him around the room.
- 온 방을 쫓아다니고?
- 그만해
Monica, please.
오빠도 좋아 죽던데?
He's totally flirting with you too.
그렇지?
He is, isn't he?
나도 모르겠어
해변에 같이 있으니까...
I don't know. Maybe it's just
being here at the beach together...
나도 모르겠어
그냥 기분이...
... but it's like something
- 안녕
Hi, Bonnie.
어서 와, 보니
사장님이 일찍 보내줘서
기차 타고 왔어
My boss let me off early,
so I took the train.
뭐하는 거예요?
What are you guys doing?
옷 벗기기 포커요
We're playing Strip Happy Days Game.
나도 해야지
Cool! I'll catch up!
그래, 내가 아직도
남자친구 감이 아냐?
So you still don't think...
...I'm boyfriend material?
어제 게임할 때
나 쳐다보는 거 봤어
I saw you checking me out
during the game last night.
넌 바지도 안 벗었잖아
You didn't even take off your pants.
다행인 줄 알아
Lucky for you.
- 뭐?
- 나도 몰라
-What?
-I don't know.
다들 재미 좋니?
Well, is everybody else having
just the best time?
조용, 조이 자잖아
Joey's asleep.
잠든 다음에 춥지 말라고
모래 덮어줬어
He passed out. We put sand
around him to keep him warm.
바퀴벌레 한 쌍은
아직이야?
Well, I assume the happy couple
isn't up yet?
Did you guys hear them last night?
어제 그 소리 들었어?
뭘 하는지 몰라도
그건 알겠더라구
I don't know what they were doing,
but sea turtles came up to the house.
바다거북이 우리 집까지
기어올라오는 거
잘 잤니?
Good morning.
- 안녕
-How'd you sleep?
-Great.
- 잘들 잤어요?
- 그럼요
Like a log.
쿨쿨 잤죠
Us too.
- 우리도요
- 우리도
난 산책이나 해야지
I'm going for a walk.
잘 잤니?
Good morning.
Nice breasts by the way.
가슴 죽인다
왜 그래요?
Hey, what happened to you?
아니에요
그냥 책이나 읽으려구요
Oh, nothing. I just felt like
hanging out and reading.
The water was so great. We jumped
off this pier and my suit came off.
물에 뛰어들어갔다
수영복이 벗겨졌지 뭐예요
Sorry I missed that.
좋은 구경 놓쳤네
조이랑 챈들러
정말 재밌어요
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
머리가 불편해서
일찍 나왔어요
I brought back half the beach
in my hair.
It was easier when I shaved my head.
머리 밀었을 땐
진짜 편했는데
있잖아요
You know, I gotta tell you...
전에 머리 없었을 때
정말 멋있었던 거 알아요?
...I just loved your look
when you were bald.
정말요?
Really?
I think about shaving it
again sometimes.
언제 다시 한번 밀어버릴까
생각 중이에요
- 정말요?
- 네
Really?
꼭 그렇게 해요
You definitely should do that.
- 그래도 될까요?
- 그럼요
You know what? I should do it!
고마워요, 레이첼
자기 정말 멋쟁이야
You know what? Thank you.
You are so cool.
그런 말 말아요
Oh, stop. Go on.
- 당장 가서 밀어버려요
- 알았어요
-Now go shave that head.
-All right.
왜 그래, 피비?
What's the matter?
She canceled.
My namesake canceled on me.
- 피비 아줌마가 약속 취소했어
- 뭐?
갑자기 시내 나갈 일이 생겼대
날 피하는 거야
She claims she had to go out of town.
She's avoiding me.
아빠가 어디 계신지
말하기 싫은 거야
She doesn't want to tell me
where my father is. She knows!
알면서 말을 않는 거라구
Pheebs, that sucks.
피비, 안됐다
Well, don't
"Pheebs, that sucks" me yet.
안됐단 말하긴 아직 일러
어디 가려고?
-Where are you going?
-She's out of town.
시내 나간 동안 집에 가서
비밀을 캐볼 거야
Something in her house
will tell me where he is.
남들은 그런 걸
무단침입이라고 부를걸
Some people call that
"breaking and entering."
너희도 그렇게 부를 거야?
Well, are any of those people here?
- 아니
- 천만에
가서 좋은 일 하면 되잖아
Look, I'll do something nice, okay?
얼음통 채워주고 올 거야
I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
Hey, everybody!
안녕
깜짝 놀랐잖아
Look what you did!
- 만져볼래?
- 아니, 어쨌든 멋지다
You wanna touch it?
No, but it's great.
만져봐
Come on, touch it.
그래
머리뼈까지 만져진다
You can feel all the bones
in your skull.
- 뭐해?
- 로스
방금 보니랑 얘기하고 왔는데
그거 알아?
I was having a little chat
with Bonnie, and guess what?
누가 머리를 밀라고 했는지
우연히 말을 하게 됐는데
She brought up who was
behind the head-shaving idea.
그게 누구였더라? 맞아
네가 밀라고 했다며?
And now, who was it?
Oh, that's right. It was you!
That was her idea.
자기가 민다고 했어
난 옆구리만 찌른 거고
I just gave her a nudge.
네가 면도날도 줬다던데
She said you gave her the razor.
So anyone up for a midnight dip?
한밤중에 수영할 사람?
-No, I'm good.
-No, thanks.
- 난 괜찮아
- 싫어요
- 그럼 나중에 봐요
- 재밌게 놀다 와
-Okay, I'll see you in a bit.
-Okay, have fun.
Come on, see?
She doesn't look that bad.
그렇게 흉하진 않잖아
달빛에 반짝이는 걸
안 봤으니까 그렇지
You can see the moonlight
bouncing off her head!
무슨 생각을 한 거야?
What were you thinking?
모르겠어
I don't know.
모르겠다고? 넌 보니를
대머리로 만들었어
You balded my girlfriend!
좋아
All right.
네가 다른 여자를 만나는 걸
보는 내 맘이 좋을 것 같아?
Do you think it's easy for me
to see you with somebody else?
끝내자고 한 건 너였어
You're the one who ended it!
너한테 화가 나서 그렇지,
널 사랑하지 않아서가 아냐
Because I was mad at you!
Not because I stopped loving you!
You still love me?
- 아직도 날 사랑해?
- 아니
날 사랑하는 거야
You still love me.
그래서 어쨌다고?
너도 날 사랑하잖아
Yeah, so?
You love me.
아니, 아...
무슨 뜻이야?
예전으로 돌아가고 싶어?
What does this mean?
I mean, do you want
to get back together?
아니, 그럴지도 몰라
No! Maybe!
I don't know.
나도 몰라, 모르겠어
로스...
네가 한 짓을
용서할 수가 없어
I still can't forgive you
for what you did.
하지만 가끔 너랑 함께
있을 때면...
But sometimes when I'm with you,
I just feel so....
뭐?
What?
기분이...
I just feel....
- 그냥...
- 뭐?
-I just
-What?
I feel
기분이...
관심 없어, 재미로 1대 1
옷 벗기기 포커는 안 한다니까
No! I don't care!
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker
with you for practice!
But I made cards!
내가 카드 만들었잖아
잘 자, 나 올라간다
Good night.
I'm going upstairs.
- 잘 자
- 안녕
-Good night.
나랑 옷 벗기기 한판 할래?
Wanna play strip poker
for practice?
내 엉덩이...
My ass!
좋아
다 됐어
저예요
소란 떨려고 한 거 아닌데!
Oh, it's me! It's me!
-I didn't wanna make any noise!
-Then don't break in!
근데 왜 몰래 들어와?
- 미안해요
- 뭐하는 거야?
-I'm sorry!
-What are you doing here?
얼음통 채워주러 왔어요
I came to fill your ice cube tray.
뭐?
What?
좋아요
Okay, look.
냉장고에서 이 사진을 떼갔어요
이 사람은 우리 아빠니까요
I took this picture from your fridge.
I know that this is my father.
This is Frank Buffay, and you were
standing next to him!
이 분은 프랭크 부페이죠
아줌마가 아빠 옆에 서있잖아요
내가 어디서 왔는지
알아야겠어요
I deserve to know where I came from.
아빠 찾는 걸 도와주세요
So if you can help me find my father,
then you should.
안 그럼 아줌마는...
나빠요
Otherwise, you're just mean.
사실대로 말해줘요
So just tell me the truth.
좋아
All right.
사진 속의 그 사람은
척 맨지오니야
The man in that picture
is Chuck Mangione.
우리 아빠가
척 맨지오니예요?
My father is Chuck Mangione?
아니, 이 사람은 척 맨지오니야
작년에 집을 팔았지
That's just Chuck Mangione.
I sold him a house last year.
그리고 미안하지만
네 아빠가 어딨는지 나도 몰라
And I'm very sorry, but I really don't
know where your father is.
정말이야
And that's the truth.
네 말이 맞아
But you're right.
네가 어디서 왔는지는
알아야지
I think a person should know
where they come from.
Which is why l....
그래서 말인데...
좋아
내가 네 엄마야
I'm your mother.
어제 얘기하고 싶었지만...
I wanted to tell you
yesterday, but I just...
너무 갑작스러워서...
...felt all floopy, and....
그럼 예전으로
다시 돌아가면 되겠네
You guys are getting back together.
아냐, 레이첼은 뭘
원하는지도 모르고 있어
She doesn't even know what she wants.
아직도 나한테 화가 나있어
Rachel's still mad at me.
그럼 모른 척 해버려
다시 상처 입을 필요 없잖아
Then you gotta back away.
You don't need that kind of hurt.
제대로 여자 한번 못 사귀어본
친구 충고를 들으라구
Take it from a guy who's...
... never had a long-term relationship.
그건 그런데...
I know, but I really want to go
up there and finish that kiss.
올라가서 하던 키스를
마저 하고 싶어
안녕
The water is great.
You should go in.
물이 굉장히 좋아요
들어가봐요
아뇨
방금 목욕했거든요
No, thanks. I just had an M&M.
그럼 잘 자요
Well, good night.
잘 자
Good night.
- 빨리 와
- 그래
Don't be too long.
Okey-dokey.
머리카락이 하나도 없다
There is not one hair on that head.
곧 자랄 거야
정말 재밌고 멋진 여자야
It'll grow back, right?
And she's really fun, and she's cool.
나도 이제 맘 잡았어
And I'm finally moving on.
레이첼을 잊을 거라구
Getting over Rachel was so
I'm finally feeling sane.
And if I go up there...
겨우 안정을 찾았는데
올라가서 키스를 하면...
...and I kiss her....
맙소사, 키스하고 싶어
하지만...
God, I want to kiss her!
잘 안 되면 어떡해
다시 마음만 아플 거야
And it doesn't work out. Do I wanna
put myself through that again?
하나만 짚고 넘어가자
Let me get this straight.
오늘밤을 보니랑 보낸다는 건
마음을 정리했다는 뜻이야
If you go with Bonnie, you do the
smart, healthy thing and move on.
레이첼이랑 보내게 되면
보니는 혼자인 거지?
Right? And if you go with Rachel,
Bonnie's free tonight?
안녕
안녕?
Hi there.
그 목소리도 이상해
That's that weird voice again.
좋아, 다시 하자, 이번엔
너도 데이트하고 싶을 거야
Let me try it again.
You'll wanna date this next guy,
I swear!
안녕, 나 난쟁이야
Hi, I'm Dorf!
너랑 데이트할 사람
Your date for the evening.
난쟁이랑 데이트하는 거
재밌잖아
Oh, come on. Dorf on dating?
That's good stuff!